africancasting.com 2018-12-22

# TitanCustomerHelp

This website (the "Site") is operated by FUSEE BVBA TitanCustomerHelp.com

We can be reached via e-mail at webmaster@titancustomerhelp.com or through our ticket support system.

This Privacy Policy Statement sets forth the policies and practices with respect to information or data gathered regarding subscribers and members of this Site. This is an adult Site that expressly and strictly limits its membership to adults. All persons under the age of 18 are strictly prohibited from accessing or viewing the contents of this Site.

This Site does not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons under the age of 18.

Notice - Use of Website by the Subscriber Constitutes the Subscriber's Express Assent to the Use of Personal Information Collected by Site.

CAREFULLY READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT BECAUSE BY YOUR SUBSCRIPTION TO AND USE OF THIS SITE YOU WILL BE EXPRESSLY SIGNIFYING THAT YOU AGREE TO THIS POLICY STATEMENT AND THAT YOU ASSENT TO THE USE OF ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT YOU SUPPLY OR THAT IS COLLECTED ABOUT YOU AS DETAILED IN THIS POLICY STATEMENT.

IF YOU DO NOT EXPRESSLY AGREE WITH ALL OF THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT YOU SHOULD NOT SUBSCRIBE TO OR USE THIS SITE.  
Information Collected:

NON-REGISTERED MEMBER: When any web user visits the site there is certain information that is collected in order to track and record visitor information and statistics. Unless the user volunatirly submits information this is limited to IP address information in order to track various statistics about the site based on all users. This information is held and shared by third parties for an unknown amount of time.

REGISTERED MEMBER: When any adult consumer signs-on as a member or subscriber of this Site that consumer will be required to provide certain personal as well as demographic information which may include, but is not necessarily limited to, the subscriber's name, address, e-mail address, username and password, and special interests or affiliations (ACCOUNT DATA). In addition to that information we may require certain credit card/payment information to allow us to process your transactions (FINANCIAL DATA) In order to better your experience on the site we may provide "cookies", track and store your IP address, etc in order to adjust the functionality of the site to your region (DEMOGRAPHIC DATA). This Site collects any and all such information and includes it in its customer database.

If the Site features or conducts any special events, special promotions or offers, contests or polls, a subscriber of the Site may be asked to provide information in order to participate, if the subscriber voluntarily provides that information, all such information may be collected by the Site and included in its customer database.

When a subscriber of this Site requests web pages from the Site's server or clicks on banners or other hypertext links, the Site will automatically collect some information or data about the subscriber, including the subscriber's IP address, the information that is collected may also indicate any special preferences or requests of the subscriber; all that information and data will be collected by the Site and included in its customer database.  
If a subscriber sends any personal communication or correspondence, by any means, to the Site, or any of its employees, agents or representatives, the Site may collect any information regarding that communication and stores that information in its customer database.  
Use of Personal Information:

ACCOUNT DATA-The information provided as account data is for the purpose of identifying the user and allow us access to a members account in order to test and confirm the functionality of various site features. You are responsible for the privacy and security of your password and account access information as this information should be kept secret from anyone besides it's intended user.

FINANCIAL DATA- The site does not store any information related to the financial data provided by you the customer (ie. credit numbers, CVV2 codes or expiration dates). This information is passed on to our payment processing partners through a PCI compliant gateway. This information may be stored for the purpose of processing any and all charges that may be generated from your membership activities on this site.

DEMOGRAPHIC DATA- We may use "cookies" and IP address information to better your experience on the site by allowing us to tailor your experience to the site according to your preferences, and what we think may appeal to you based on such demographic information. The "cookies" are set to track voting, session usage, and various other features that exist within the site. The IP address information is used to analyze traffic trends, perform regional customization and in some cases allow us to alter the presentation of the site to better match your demographics.  
Security of Personal Information Collected by the Site:

Consistent with the Policies set forth in this Privacy Statement, the Site has adopted and implemented reasonable and technologically feasible procedures for maintaining the security, accuracy and integrity of all personal information relating to subscribers that is collected by the Site. All personal information will be secure and treated as confidential. No personal information will be shared with third parties without the customer's permission  
"OPT-IN" Provisions:

There may be occasions when a subscriber will be presented with special offers either from the operators of the Site or from third-party service or content providers, which may include consent to receive e-mail solicitations, communications, newsletters, commercial advertising, or other promotional or special event materials (collectively referred to as "Offers").

"OPT-IN" -- Some Offers may be presented to the subscriber with the option to express the subscriber's preference by either clicking or entering "accept" (alternatively "yes") or "decline" (alternatively "no"). By selecting or clicking the "accept" or "yes" the subscriber indicates that the subscriber "OPTS-IN" to that Offer and thereby agrees and assents that the subscriber's personal information and data may be disclosed to third-parties.  
Terms and Conditions of Membership:

Each subscriber should carefully read each of the terms and conditions of Membership of this Site. By accepting membership to this Site you are unconditionally accepting all of those terms and conditions. Some of those terms and conditions may also affect the right of this Site to use information that it has gathered from subscribers.

By completing the membership form you are agreeing to the terms of this agreement. These terms and conditions can be changed at the discretion of titancustomerhelp. It is up to each individual to refer to this page for any amendments. Once you have submitted the join form you have become a 'member'.

As a member you are responsible for paying periodic membership fees.

For your convenience and satisfaction, all memberships will automatically renew upon expiration unless your subscription is cancelled at least 5 days prior to the end of the current term.

To cancel your membership, simply follow the cancellation link found on the support, or join page. Cancellations will not be accepted via email. The cancellation form is a simple process!

Any liability of including without limitation under any course of action will be limited to the amount paid by a member for the preceding 12 months.

Members user name and password must not be distributed to others. This will result in immediate suspension of service. under law must hold the member liable for unauthorized breach of membership.

Password protection software is installed to keep the cost of the site down. Members who download more than a 6000 Megabytes per day (about 60 complete videos), or who log in from many different subnets, will have their username blocked for 24 hours.

All information transmitted via email is deemed public domain material. For your convenience your email will be added to our newsletter list which you can opt out of at anytime. We will not share your personal information with anyone. Memberships are not transferable.

We do not provide support for download management tools or download accelerators. Read support link or contact tech support for accepted or required software.

Members are responsible to provide all necessary equipment to gain access to titancustomerhelp websites. Ttitancustomerhelp has the right to refuse membership to any individual and has the right to cancel a membership. Without limitation does not offer any warranty to any aspect of the service be it a service provided directly by or a 3rd party source.

All pictures, images, sounds, text, video-caps, and any other material located on this site are the sole property of and are not to be distributed in any form without the prior written consent of . All videos and photos are for personal use only. Members and former members are not allowed to share or trade the photos or videos from the site via P2P networks, trading sites or reselling our content in any other way. The site is the only place to see our exclusive movies and photos.

Extreme care must be taken for members to make sure that none of the photos or videos are viewed by anyone under the age of 18 years old. By joining this site you declare, under penalty of perjury, that you are at least 18 years old, and are not offended by sexually explicit material and are legally able to view/download such items according to the laws by which you are governed.

Under the penalty of perjury:

(1) I am an adult aged 18 years or older.  
(2) I have come to knowing it's contents and agree to view sexually explicit material for my personal use. Viewing such material does not knowingly violate the community standards of the area in which I live.  
(3) I will not exhibit the images of to minors or anyone else who might be offended by them. Please protect your username and password so that accidental access is prevented.

Refund Policy:

You hereby acknowledge and agree that if you cancel your subscription or if your subscription is canceled by the company, your password will be removed from the system at the end of the then current monthly membership period and that you will be entitled to receive the full benefits of your subscription until the end of such period. You will NOT be entitled to any pro-rated or partial refund if YOU cancel your monthly subscription before the end of the then current monthly subscription period for any reason.

Subscribers acknowledge Membership subscriptions gain instant unrestricted access to the website until canceled.

This Agreement in its entirety contains the entire agreement between the member and titancustomerhelp. Any questions regarding this Agreement should be sent to webmaster@titancustomerhelp.com.
